Tell me how you think I'm wrong, when I say I feel so lost
Tell me why you think you're love, erase all that it cost
Tell me why you look at me, like I'm just a piece of dust
Tell me how you think you know, when I give away my trust
Tell me how I'm
Yeah, yeah, that is annoying. It's like it. I don't because I don't know if it was like the I
Just remember like when I hit the person on at the last second
I was like, oh damn it. They're a form bomber and then I took it off and then someone was like, oh, well
They I saw a way and I didn't know
Really, I don't think I got my glasses on but we got everything back up. We're just gonna fix it real quick
And there we go. We got a
Back he went up guys. Hello
Hi, I do that pretty quick. I'm able to I'm not gonna ask you what happened because you know playing against you as
Well, it's just like I think there might have been a porn bomb
I'm not sure but it's like if it's gonna take a chance
An hour
Yeah, because people have actually had them had their channels like just deleted because of a porn bomb
If they didn't get it fast
That's why I stopped doing panels. Yeah, it's hard. It's a risk. It's a risk
It's hard
That's why I stopped going tanners
Sponky's game poor mom and I did form them over a hundred times
I'm always able to like, you know delete the stream one time
I was that you know and they deleted the stream for me basically like you know
So I need to be careful like to I think I deleted the the wrong stream or something like that like
your overlays we heard well I mean it's like that was like cuz I know the name I recognize the name but
then I remembered it the last second but that was like a porn bomber that uses the name and stuff
it's I remember I was just like kind of like unconscious and I usually do use the overlay
I just like he did it to me too I think psyche he thought he thought I was a porn bomber he took
me off I think there's one problem which
Think there's one problem here. It's like yeah, I think that you it's kind of like her like don't let the same people up here
Yeah, I know
Some important bombs as long as you take it down quickly
Yeah, I know but the but Brian like the one time like I got like you know
They've deleted it for me was I thought I deleted it
But it deleted like some other video like it hadn't queued up as like the last video yet
And so I think so it's just like that was a flirty diamond time where she like was like rubbing her things balloon under her dress
And then flash her boobs and
Whatever that yeah, that was that day that yeah a whole prior problem. I thought that was not real
It was a it was like a balloon animal
Yeah, yeah, yeah, and she kept doing it and I kept saying stop and then she flashed her boobs and stuff
But she was really drunk and we've since she apologized for that and stuff, but yeah, it was kind of like
I remember you did that to me. Disgusting.
You thought, yeah, I was on, I was on, I was showing the picture and then he.
Yeah.
Closed, like he put something on it.
And disrespect for my boys, Shannon, you got to do it on my boys.
You know, he thought, he thought, he thought, he thought I was on poor mama.
And he just, he just shade it.
Yeah
I
Remember when I remember when I first joined member everybody was like saying like oh, like you're the one that strike channel member all that
Yeah
You
Do you want to see some titties now?
Like when Janet was like, you know when I met Janet like we were like, you know got pretty wild on the show
I was like drinking a lot more
Yeah, yeah, it was working. It's just working in all hell bro. It was all over everywhere
She was shaking
Like water
You're a camera. If you can camera for a second, let me see. You look like but yeah
Oh
Everyone make it. I'll just be naked. Yeah, we want to see some ass. Not you have nothing that we know
I'm pitching in here right now
You know what the fuck you talking about ghost? Well, I mean I don't want to be nervous
Pitchering a woman he would never want to picture you
No, oh, no, yes
I've seen him on camera. He came he came up for me before and like show me like, you know
Yeah, you did I saw it. No, I saw you on a different show. You know you came to my different show
And I was like, why is he came up with me? I saw you on beaters. I saw you on beaters
I swear to God he did I swear
He was throwing it in a circle.
He was throwing it back there.
Yeah, he was throwing it.
Yeah, he was throwing it in a circle.
He was throwing it back there.
Yeah, he was throwing it.
Yeah, he was throwing it in a circle.
That was you double cheeked up on a fucking Tuesday. Oh, that was you girls
You was double cheek. The year on that purpose that you was on that purpose thing. No, no, no
I wasn't looking sir. I glanced over and he was on the whole lot of answer
Double cheek
That's what I said my sorry about that. Okay. Whoa. Whoa. I
Quote myself sir. Thank you. Thank you
I'm used to talking like that in different panels, but it's like you don't allow them. I understand
I understand. Okay. So listen, sir. We don't care
Listen, sir. When we're not a little thick boy. You're a little thick boy. We don't care when I can't do
Yeah, I saw you because I was after my show one night and you were on like
Another show and you and you came up for a second. I was like, why are you heating camera on my show?
I was like, why is he like came up here?
Yeah
No, it was a picture is it was actually you were standing by buy a car or something like that outside and I saw you
Hold on. I'm gonna show you
Trying to prove them so you're run by car. Oh, there's some cool
I know, I still wanted my reading.
You got it. Okay. I had the third card for you Janet was or this is seek
It's a seek someone to perform a cord-cutting ritual
So I think that like maybe either you or learn how to do it or it's like you find it
And it says they're recruiting they're recruiting haters, okay, they are by the moment honey
They type in fast honey, they get up and wake up about miss Brittany, honey
But continue. I'll say they will play victim once they know they're losing
Okay
And then real time if they ever tried it, but you know, this one says unintentional
They don't realize they're sending you the evil words and actions
And so it might be an intense some of this might be unintentional like some of this might follow
They have no thought of their own so right and I'm not a cult leader
I'm all for free will which is something they you know don't value in themselves because that's our power
But yeah, but then they're like finally we have this one is it's his own worst enemy
It says you cause most of your problems or most of the bad things that happen to you yourself
Then this is true for everybody though, you know, it's like we are
Because I allow them to take the kindness and then they take it for you know weakness and then I can react
So I appreciate that. Thank you. Thank you John John to Brittany. Oh, thank you
Yeah, you have a question though. When the other time
No, go ahead. What's your question?
Um, because I did join your uh panel earlier
Yeah, and you were uh, uh, you were reading like some sculpture. Uh
I just wonder why you did that you actually believe are you religious at all?
I was scripture. I was reading scripture. I was reading the Psalms. I was reading some Psalms, right?
Yes, sir. You did. Yes. Yeah, I like I know I like I like I'm a lot of the bible
I think and I think the Psalms are also these beautiful prayers. I have a lot of power
Oh, the there's like rainbows going on my wall right now. I can show you hold on
Yeah, I think but I think yeah, I mean the bible is like a beautiful book
You know it has power in it and there's power in the words there's power in like belief and it's like those are
Psalms are a kind of blessings like or like prayers
Protect from harm and from enemies and from evil eye and all kinds of stuff in there
So they're very useful. They use them in all kinds of different contexts too
And so maybe I don't necessarily believe in the traditional christian manner, but I respect your
Your whole panel is a tarot
Sure, it's compatible with Christianity. It's compatible with Christian. There's biblical tarot decks. There's tarot decks that have like, you know
Psyche, why are you on the day you run? You run my arm one of the cards, right?
And you told me to be careful. What that means. You were trying to be careful to be careful
Well, it's like, you know, just to like
Don't be reckless in life and don't don't make like obviously done mistakes and like
And like, you know, be careful who you like, you know
Watch your way and all that stuff
Yeah, it's just like all it is is like just being like respect other people. Yeah, and also you're keeping your eyes open
Let me see. Oh, yeah, this is this is a
I'm busy bro. Hurry up
Hello, I'm busy. Hurry up. Oh, yeah, you're here. You're on this. They're on the air
You're trying to hurry up
Fuck you. Hello
Yo, what's up, dude
Hi, how are you?
Do you know Janet? I'm busy hurry up. You talked about random guy earlier psyche by the way. What the fuck did he say? I
Said that I saw you talking shit about me on a show about
You don't know what the fuck you're talking about. Yeah, absolutely no clue what you're doing you come up here to start trouble
Now go stop here. Now what are you gonna do random guy? Let's run it. Let's run it
Yeah, let's run it
Listen, you don't know what the fuck you're talking about about anything name one thing
You always say that you say the same thing over you're played out. Yeah, I say the same thing
I can back it up. See I can back it up with that here. What are you backing up? Oh
Thank you don't know what the fuck you're talking about sir
You don't know what you're talking about you come up here to cause trouble the same
I come up here to call trouble. All right. Well, you're not going to switch it up send them some more money
I'm sending some more money. I also do it. I mean what what what I'll send him more money. Why are you out?
Yeah, go you about it. Oh, what's the lady? What's the lady talking about you about it?
What's wrong with me? That's a good. I mean, what's wrong with me send the sake you money? That's my
Money sounds some more. Thank you. I love you guys. No, I appreciate everything. I appreciate it. Okay, random guy now go stop here now
I'm gonna
Now, it goes up here now. What the fuck is you talking about?
Right? What the fuck?
Uh-oh.
Straight up. What the fuck are you talking about, random guy?
I thought I want nothing you join a couple panels talking shit. Now you're here now
You owe me
You literally said psyche was your bit you've my hate more money than you never once said
For two months. How is he your bitch? I gave more money than you. How is he your bit? No, you didn't know you by the way
No, what'd you send?
He did some more. Yes, I keep work. Yes, like he can you compare that how much money do I send compared to him?
I mean, I'm pretty sure I sent more, but you know, I might be wrong, but go ahead and compare it. I
Can't hear it. Too much. You're my bitch. I'll be okay. I'll be
Straight up
You're a fucking bitch. Don't don't ever talk. It's like you don't ever let him talk to you like that
Listen, I want to say
You don't know what the fuck you're talking about random guy
You dumb fuck
You just went in a fucking loop
You don't know what the fuck you're talking about. See you had
And it comes back to you. You still don't know what the fuck
Still in you don't know what the fuck you're talking about. There we go again. Same. Are you really bad?
Are you really that part of it? I can't do this for this guy. I can't do this. Yeah, you can't do it
That's why I'm here because you're too fucking stupid to have it weird
Yeah, yeah, you did it with psyche. You did it with a lot of people. You're not gonna do it with me
Do what? Oh shit. Oh shit. Come up here and talk shit. You're
Good you can't even know you can't even go with me
Let's run it let's fucking go
Let's run it little boy
He said you said it's a circle listen. I said you were tired at the beginning a fucking we ran that circle and guess what?
I ended with you retard it obviously it's a full circle or you two
Your big-ass bitch
Trollin because you can't have the argument
Now you're going to trolling because you you don't understand what the fuck we're talking about sir
You ain't talking about shit, bro. You're it. Yeah, I'm talking about you are too fucking stupid to have the conversation, sir
Oh, oh, it's okay be a dump. It's okay. He got him. It's okay. Be done. It's okay to be a dumb dumb
You try to bully psyche
Ghosts here, but it's okay. It's okay. Be dumb dumb. I'm too dumb for this one. I'm dumb dumb. I'm dumb dumb
This dude is fucking
I'm a dumb dumb, too
We all don't know what the fuck he's talking about he comes up here
You should be you should feel thankful that he didn't let you on his fucking panel. You're a fucking William
He owes me he's my bitch
Yeah, he's your bitch
How is it your bitch? You're on this panel you dumb fuck. How much money did you pay?
He needs the content, because he can't do it himself.
How much money did you pay?
Well, you are the contestant, right?
And I paid a lot. Personally, I did pay a lot.
You're the dummy.
Am I?
I'm an idiot!
Psyche, he's not my bitch. I paid a lot of fucking money to drop my bitch.
That's Joe. That's Joe.
Psyche's not my bitch.
No, I'm talking to Ryan. Let me talk to random guy.
Okay, I'm talking to Joe.
I'm talking to Joe. You're talking to Joe.
Well, Joe can get it to you, but I'm talking to random guy right now
Talking about random guy if you stupid to have the conversation random guy talk to me bitch
Yeah, what was your argument?
Explain
You want me to talk shit do you want me?
He's actually got nothing. Yeah, you're retarded. You don't know what you're talking about. You're dirty. You're crusty. You know, you're dirty.
You're butthole. I mean, really, you want me to get that bad down? Bad down? Yes.
Why don't you come up here and cough like you're a bitch again, because it's not going to work out. You fucking retard.
Why are you so mad about this? Why do you get so mad, ghost?
I want you
Okay, random guy, why do you suck some random dick for and what would you get mad when I say that?
Why are you so mad?
You just make shit up
What is this what kind of relationship to you it's like you really have
Now
They come down on it. You ain't gonna take on me
You're you you are
Ghosts fucking dick
How many dicks did you suck sir?
Actually, we're not making it up. Yeah psych is your bitch, but guess how many dicks you see how quick
He's like a logic. We're like, I'm gonna blow job right now ghost
Yeah, you know
Yeah, he comes in peace
I don't. I don't. I don't.
I don't.
I don't. to the master. You're
How many digs did you suck and do you suck it from the back sir?
I don't know. I don't. I don't
I don't know. I don't know. I
Hey, you're the one sentence like he thousands of dollars a week and do you slot do you slobber on it, sir?
You're the one sentence like he thousands of dollars a week
The proof is in the money. I've never once said proof is in the money
It's all on this and sir I can help you out. It's all like you help me up to psyche
I ever sent you a thousand dollars
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I ran you dude. It's done. That's all that's all
Going in circles about it
Your bitch
I've been waiting for you brother been waiting
Hey, I'm still here wait a couple hours, but now you're here now. I got a fucking listen. I'm here proof of him being my bitch
How how explain how burn the proof is on you house you bitch
Because psyche let you up. He's your bitch. Let you up. Let's go. He said
Go wait. No. No. No. How is psyche your bitch?
Let me handle this fucking fool
He let you up on his fucking over panel. He was gracious enough to let you up. And now he's your bitch
Now he's forced him to let me back on proof of him being my bitch again
You know what?
Yeah. Yeah. He's the losing one. Yeah. Yeah. Bye bye random. Bye bye random.
Unless you want to actually have a debate. You're a random guy. We can run it. Let's run it.
I don't want to waste it. I don't
want to waste it. But content
round three motherfucker. We got
round three. My big ding ding
No
I already got a psyche. Can you please explain in New York? I got one more
on our cash out
To New York. I don't know about cash up. I'll allow you to receive
I can look it up. I think it's like a lot a large amount. It's a large amount. It's like $100,000.
I'm looking right now. I'm looking right now. It's definitely not a hundred K. I sent a lot of money on cash out before.
Not to some fucking loser online, but to make money, but to actually make money with that money.
How did you make money? Tell me, bitch.
Look at what I said, bitch. Tell me.
What do you mean bitch once you explain to me tell me round for make money
He's my big I send a lot of money in the psyche and guess what I'm not making from psyche money
That's his money cheeks because he's stuck in your dick
that
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I don't know. I don't know.
That was five. That's why you did that to me. That's my stuff because he's a boss. Listen,
I would I would if it's like he's paying all I would let him back if he's not making an
argument though. I just keep winning. He's talking shit.
Yeah, he's like I keep letting it back on to like say something else in New York. It is you know, I am it's free speech New York
Oh, I'm down to talk to him, but he don't what he don't want to talk you just he doesn't make sense every time
I prove a point he just wants to argue. It's like dude. You've been proven wrong
easy work and
New York you don't like it I
Like it. It was fun. Oh
It's funny. Well, listen, I mean, it's free. It's a psyches panel, but
Me personally, it's free speech. You say whatever the fuck you want, but when I prove a point, you know, I'm saying like
Did she come back already? Like I'm proving a
Who?
random guy
Do I have a can I say what can I kick them off then?
Yeah, yeah bring him back bring him back here rounds round six me proving that he's my bitch
All right, dude listen, you're not gonna say dude's like you go now you're not gonna say that how was like
So so I use your bitch because he brought you back cuz it was actually he's it brought you back
So therefore you're my bitch you're fucking me there for you're my that's why therefore you're my bitch
I brought you back. I'm the one that you and I'm the one that brought you back. You're my bitch then
No, you ain't doing so you're my bitch. Good boy
That's a good dog. Are you a goth guy? All right, it's fucking owns you anything else you want to say it is fucking
You're my boy good boy, you'll be broke soon, dude
You'll be broke. Okay. Good boy. Hey, no more power
I got it. You have no more power.
Good boy. You didn't make a fucking argument. You you try to come up here and call Psychic.
You can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't
you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't you can't
I'm giving you whenever I see you alone on the panel with psyche
It's like creeps me out a little bit like I have to go to a different stream
Because it's too gay for me. Good argument. What's your argument? Yeah
That was it. Do you want me on the map? Okay, cool. I'll give you that. You and him together. What's your argument?
Yeah, what's your argument? You know, I gotta go another stream. Okay, then leave. I don't even have to pay to get you then this leaves. Bye, bitch
No, we got more people here. I'm comfortable now. You retard it. You just said you
Here now you want to be here. No, I'm saying when
Like a love fest. It's like a gay little love. I've never I've never
Everyone it just means like I see it all the time. So when the fuck was that so when was that when did you join?
You and psyche together
You're talking about dude. Yeah, you talk shit about psyche. You like the bullet
I love you too. Let's run it. You don't know what you're talking about. Dang explain yourself, please
Explain yourself
Listen, let me tell you a little fucking argument works
If you make a claim the burden of proof is on you and you haven't proved nothing, okay, right?
Yeah, I know the same stick. I don't know if you have a ritual
Do you have a the same stick written down?
At least I come fresh every single day you don't
You call it
Dude you're
Never switch it up
Boring there. I said it now what but I can run with you
See that night
Now I want you here drown your fucking son. I'll return it. You are you are given
Suck my dick you open them out by the way
You're too stupid to have the conversation sir
So shut the fuck up and be glad to be up here
Which you never should have done it now I'm here you should have you should have never done it dude
Everyone knows like he's my bitch. He's everyone's bitch
Everyone you want me to burn you up again how many times I do it you're only in there my bitch random guy
You're my $200 goes for two months my bitch prove me wrong. You're my bitch. Put me wrong. Hey attention
I pulled you you're my bitch for me wrong now. You're not gonna date. You're my bitch for me wrong. I
Just fucking you're my you're my bitch prove me wrong
You're not gonna run away from it
This is there my bitch permit wrong is terrible. You're my bitch
You're my bitch
You are my bitch
Would you like me to spell it out for you?
No, are you sober?
My bitch psychies everyone's bitch. No, you're my no, no, no
I'm not saying I'm you're my bitch. You are special. You're my bitch, sir
Because he's your bitch too. You're my bitch. It's not he's definitely not you're my bitch
You won't touch him. I'm like, and you know, you're my bitch. You know, you're my bitch
Beedah, I don't give a fuck. You're rotten fucking you're a bitch. Well, she can join
She said you are my bitch fuck you so she's a real one for that you're gonna let these
And we don't give a fuck, that's another creator, we don't care, you're my bitch, you're running, you're so, you're running, she said go fuck it Rock, is this dude not running, you're my bitch, you are my bitch, you're running, you're my bitch, he's on the run, you're running
You are running absolutely you are running take your money. You are running from our you are running
Sike, no, I just flipped it on you. I've never actually he's literally running. I took my argument
You're you're a further idiot. It's called
Shut the fuck up and listen to me. No ass. I'm not so I keep your eyes. Oh, I work
Drunk to idiot
Fucking Richard
he ran
He ran
Jesus Christ. I'm never won. I've never you know, I'm not trying. I'm not trying to bully on the guy. I
Already won. I'm not trying to bully him. I'm not trying to bully him, but actually psyche psyche
I was bullying him because he psyche memory did you he's like, oh
Remember he like you're my bitch. You're my bitch. Why did I did the exact same thing to him?
Exactly psyche's my bitch. Well, all right, go ahead. Go see her now
All of a sudden I'm not your bitch all of a sudden you become my bitch
Like beating up on psyche fucking me
Janet sorry. Yeah, New York. Sorry
Nope, you're fine
Been fun
But New York he did random guy was talking shit. He kept saying he was talking shit like yeah
Psychies my bitch psyche my bitch psyche talking about the earlier and I was like, dude. Yeah, but now you're my bitch, sir
That he was on another panel
And he didn't want to address that so he should address what sites it
Why were you talking shit about him when I'm on the panel? I think that's I think that's I think that's fair
Yeah, I think that's where he started from Matt and started attacking and he got what he got and he didn't win anything
The fuck is he delusional?
Fucking if he wants to be fair, I'll run it with him the third time, but he's not gonna do it
he changed okay he got proven wrong got any change what about beta nobody gives a
fuck you just call my boy a bitch I'm not gonna bring up other people you're a
bitch there yeah exactly that's what he that's what he does I mean I'm gonna call
my boy a bitch while you suck and suck he's dying suck and nothing you're a
bitch boy I mean this shit is easy
Anything to get rid of the people that care about is like
I'm gonna get out of here
Always
What? Wait a minute. You leave me. You don't own this. I was just talking with you.
No, you're cute. Don't worry about it. You're good. I appreciate it. Call my boy a bitch again.
What the fuck? Thank you so much. I love you too. Like, I'll be, I'll see you again, sweetheart.
Okay, have a good night. Have a good night, man.
Yeah
No, my bad. No, my bad. I met no versus back. He called my boy a bitch
He cuts like you bitch, so I was just hanging on that
And people call me a lot of stuff. I really don't care. It's like words on her
But I don't get offended by people calling me names because it's like, you know, there's just their own
Listening right now
Okay, I don't run it with anybody that wants it
You know people are kind of mean to me like I've noticed like just like mean to me like it's like
You're my bitch, but they're not gonna fucking and make the argument about it like they're just like let's run it
Yeah, they won't me it's like and it's like always gonna be like he's not gonna do it by the way
It's like he I never heard argument why you're his bitch by the way
Never
I'm not is he thinks because I mean it's like people donate money
It's like I appreciate that I appreciate it sometimes it's for a reason sometimes it's for other things
But it's like I appreciate it, but it's like it doesn't make me a bitch
You know, it's like sometimes people like I think yeah, I'll give a million dollars
Still your channel. I love you. Yeah. Yeah, it's like you threw me in the air
No, I love I love all you guys and it's like, you know, I don't need it
It's like you guys are just keeping me alive. Hey, you know my neighbor
I actually want to give the people what they want they want to hear an argument and stuff
But I cannot argue for in a practice. It's not an argument. He's just there's not an argument
Yo, yo, thank you. You're my mom must handle for me
I'm kind of busy on my own. I'm bet it's like yeah, but I could give you some hits and like tips and stuff
Have you I'm gonna have you on
Control my not control myself. I'm gonna let you I'm gonna let you go. I'm like I say this shit
Know how you do your panel? I'm gonna yeah when I'm not around like you do my panel for me
Okay, well you can always um you can always connect that on stream yard
You can connect my show to your show and like stream me they can restream me
I don't I don't I don't I don't know how to do that
Just go in stream yard and you go like restreet. Yeah, you just going oh you're in stream out right now
So you just go into like restream this channel or something like that
There's like some option for that. I think but I'll figure we'll figure it out. Yeah, I'll help you
Yeah, I'm trying to learn I'm trying to learn a lot of stuff cuz I don't like I don't do panels no more
Like I do panels and that's sometimes I don't
Like people don't come up, you know
You have to put an open panel into the ship
Ghost never come up to my panel
You have to put an open panel in your title. I'll run it. Your ghost is two different things ghost
On the one I got under my name. That's not mine. That's somebody else
That's because you joined somebody else who I did somebody else who I joined with but you know, um, I
Got my own thing. It's like two different things
No, the on the name on the bottom the bottom is somebody else on podcast, you know, I mean well panel whatever you want to call it
You know me
Well, I mean, if you are getting strong someone out, you're, you're, like, I represent something guilty, aren't you?
I represent, I represent, I represent that panel too. You don't represent nothing.
Yes, I do I represent any pen. You know, I mean, I I represent psyche because I'm here to defend them
Dude, you use this bitch. I just had a fucking argument about it
Yeah, no, but ghost the ghost what I'm talking about is like, you know how everybody
Subscribe on people that you know, they follow them and they watch their videos
That's all I do. I followed them watch the videos and I go into the panels. That's all
Yeah
Yeah, yeah, I don't play I don't play like and they're kind of I don't like comments and other comments here
Just because it's like, you know, I have too many people like trying to like strike me and stuff
So it's kind of not safe to my bad. I want blood
Somebody's gonna call my dear
No, but no, no, but I've seen ghosts like you don't go outside and
And film police and all of that stuff, you know, he do his god damn
We don't I have I have I have filmed the police
But it's like in a friendly way like when they've been like, you know resting somebody and there's been like a lot of them around
No, I think it's not like it's not like to bother them
The auditing you're having the auditing the auditing, right? Yeah, all right. Yeah, like your first memory, right?
You got right. Yeah, the cops you got right from the government people
Where they kind of yell at the cops at the same time, but even they do that so the cops get kind of mad, right? Yeah
You know, I watch stuff like that and, you know, I, um, I go to that guy, um, my boy's
panel, you know what I mean?
Yeah.
And then I go, you know, when he's not around, when your panel's on, I go to your panel,
and when his panel's on, I go to his panel.
So, like, you know, I ran him guy back up here.
He's, I don't think he's backstage.
Let me see.
You know, he's not backstage.
No, I go to a different panel and I don't promote any panels, you know, I mean, yeah
If I do my own panel, I say yo, if I'm doing my own panel and I say yo shout out to psyche panel
You know, or shout out to you know people podcast or shout out to Miguel's panel, you know, I mean
Yeah, you promote other people
I do too I try to promote everybody like that people like they can post their channels in here
Most people are mods or they can let the mod know or they can at least put their channel name into the chat and stuff
So yeah, I want people to be successful here. I think I said say like summer last night
I want people to be making money too. I want I think the panel panels
Panel hosts like people really like the panels a lot of people do already donate. I think uh
I think that uh people like your summer like I want her to make more money and like I want other people if they
Want you to be able to like monetize their channel and I think it's it's fun. Yeah
They can come back up, but yeah, I haven't seen them down there. So is he is he in the chat? I don't see him
Okay
Next you can come up to here and I think you know, I think psyche is mad cool, you know me
Oh, thank you. There's a couple panels. I know they cool people
Yeah, I can never be suspected me. I mean
Thank you. Yeah, I mean if I respect
Yeah, I get if I get to know everything
Hey, New York, can I ask you a question? How do you feel about that dude saying that uh, it's like he says bitch
that's what he said. That's
That doesn't mean it doesn't mean anything. I posted something last night that says a fool gets upset when people
When he gets upset with people aren't trying to talk about when they are trying to defend
I say like this if I say your ghost your mother fucker you my bitch and I fucked you in your ass
You'll get I can defend myself
No, you offend yourself, but I can defend myself. No. Yes. That's what I said, but my eyes
You'll get mad when the guy was saying that I'm talking shit about psyche. What the fuck are you talking about?
No, no, no, I don't know. I don't understand that. But if the guy's saying that about psyche and psyche is not getting mad, he doesn't say that.
Why I don't care. I don't care. I don't care
I mean, I don't care that what people call me because I have been called a lot of stuff and it's like it doesn't affect me
But it's still pretty rude to say it on my panel. Yeah, it's not respectful to me
Exactly. It's fucking rude. It's disrespectful. No, that is what we discuss. You know, I mean, but what it is what it is
Yeah, I'm gonna say I'm making the excuse for it. I don't get it. I'm gonna fend it
I just like I just think it just shows its ignorance and it's like, you know, it's not great doesn't make him look very good
So just cuz he doesn't go fuck. It's not rude
Yeah, it is rude. I mean it's like but it's like it doesn't hurt. You're a ghost. How many times you drink a lot, right?
There's no disrespect to you, bro. Like I'm cool with you. Yeah, you don't know what the fuck you're talking about.
How many times you told somebody to suck your dick from the back and the person didn't do nothing.
Oh, one time. One time. Because I like to suck dicks from the back. I said that one time.
I said it one time. New York. I said it one time. You said it. You said it a couple times, brother. I ain't gonna lie. I said it one time.
But no, you said it a couple times. Now that she made me laugh. Okay, go ahead and prove it.
That's you. That's you. No, I'm not proving nothing. I said it one time, literally. No, the way you say it, no, the way you say it.
So now, New York, no, listen, you don't even know what the fuck you're talking about. Goals, I'm not arguing with you, bro.
Let's not go. She can say go so you want. No, we're not gonna run back.
said it one but you will you say you say suck my dick from the back is funny the way you say it
yeah one time i said it one time no you said it a couple times bro not only one time i got
psyche is that true did i say it more than once i don't know i don't know you know you know you
know i don't fucking remember i said it one time no you never said it you said it in psyche panel
once but you said it in the fucking i said it twice what's your problem with it you said it a
couple times my nigga different pain all right fucking i said it three times what's your problem with it
No, I'm just saying you get man. Okay. Well, I said it three times. What's your problem? No, you say me like a hundred times
What I had a problem with they call yeah, you're gonna hurt
They call my boy psyche a bitch and that's what I'm here for and nobody's on my bitch
Yo, but yo, that's what the fuck is you talking about yo you my bitch
I said suck my dick from back one time. Now you're gonna be butthurt about it. New York really
You too by the way, if you're gonna be
You sound like a bitch
You sound like a by the way random guy is my bitch, but you sound you sound kind of dumb
You're my ho ho ho, you're my ho ho ho, you're my ho ho ho, you're my ho ho ho, you're my ho ho ho, you're my ho ho ho, you're my ho ho ho, you're my ho ho ho, you're my ho ho ho, you're my ho ho ho, you're my ho ho ho, you're my ho ho ho, you're my ho ho ho, you're my ho ho ho, you're my ho ho ho, you're my ho ho ho, you're my ho ho ho, you're my ho ho ho, you're my ho ho ho, you're my ho ho ho, you're my ho ho ho, you're my ho ho ho, you're my ho ho ho, you're my ho ho ho, you're my ho ho ho, you're my ho ho ho, you're my ho ho ho, you're my ho ho ho, you're my ho ho ho, you're my ho ho ho, you're my ho ho ho, you're my ho ho ho
Yeah, okay, you're fucking retarded. You have no idea
Yeah, I'm getting my thought you need New York, you know, New York. I thought it was smart, but you know, they are dumb in New York
You're I sound just like you you're okay. What are we talking about sir? What are we talking about right now?
What are we talking about? Your butthurt your butthurt's that's what we talking about
God damn
The least random guy was a retard. You're just a retard. You don't even know it
Yeah, you are dumb dumb sir, you're dumb dumb
Yeah
Yeah, you don't know you don't know
Dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb you like your dumb dumb
Just like you call my boy just like they try to call my uh, just like they try to call my boy psyche a bitch and guess what happened
They got fucking served up
Or you like by the way psyche am I wrong for defending you about that?
No, it's his panel
But maybe I'm wrong. All right. You should be happy. You're not wrong. I'm saying you're not wrong. All right be happy
Thank you, sir. Yeah, are you good? Yeah, he goes
Yeah, no second second those butthoops
Ghost you need me to have it some more. I said let random guy back up here, but he's not
Even this bass on me on his butt. Well anybody else wants it let him up psyche if you don't mind it
Okay, nobody's nobody's
Your eggy
hold on
You're listening to this right? Yeah, I'm gonna tell this man watching listen your eggy
Watch I want this thing to come watch. Hold on. Your eggy come here.
You know, you know, you know,
He's right next to me right next to me though. Is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is he is
He said yo the guy said fuck you you're hurt the guy said fuck you you're hurt. I'm not selling him for an M. Yard
King David
I'm not giving you my money. You'll pop in my shit soon
So I keep by the way if anybody else calls you a bitch. I got you. Thank you, dude. Yo, yo ghost you mother
Yeah, her ghost
I'm drinking some liquor and I'm calling you my bitch
Yeah
So I keep did anybody else want to
Nobody has nobody else is coming up. I guess tonight
But guys if you do what if you guys if you're I'm doing I'm doing a spiritual counseling session
I'll do it twice as long. It's open panel
But if you guys are interested just hit me up on that cash up and I'll I'm scheduled within 24 hours
An hour to talk with the police and send you know
Hey, Paula said they he was backstage
He was I
Try again. I don't see I didn't see I have to be like look at this
Excuse me
Are you burp?
Yeah, I'm going to her screen see 14 viewers enjoyed the blood money
Random guy. I literally you're allowed back up here. Why are you fucking super chatting? You're allowed back up here
Super chat. He's gonna be super chat home. No, he's been super. Yeah. Thank you. Thank you, dude. Oh
It's fine. I mean a 26 viewers right now
Random guys here. Can I kick go next you can kick ghost but talk to psyche and ask how much? Yeah?
I mean, yeah, but you can literally kick me. Yes, you can do it
There's the gong it's like $25 the catchups on the screen go ahead and hit that up if you're
How much money do I have to pay them? Can I bring can I bring necks up here?
How much money do I have to spend for that? I have to ask necks
How much how much if you doing it to next how much money you get next please answer?
$200 $200 right now. No, I'm talking about next how much money? Yeah, $200. Oh
Damn
And then then you get the hell out your her ghost will kick you the fuck out
You're gonna kick me out sir
Hey, I'll give I'll give psyche 20 dollars. No, I am leaving. All right. I'm leaving
Come on, I'm just messing with me. Just love your ghost come back up, bro. You're a hater ghost come on
Hi
Okay, you don't pay your hundred dollars. You don't kick me out. I'm leaving
Because if you do that if you do donate if you do donate for something goes
Can you please hit the cash app and like I think it's better than the super chat because I know yeah, that's facts
Yeah
But however you want to say they said it's not working. They said it's not working
Okay, the cash app isn't oh, no, I'm sorry. It is
It's not working
Well, let me see if I got the right address on PSY CHE awakens. Yeah, it should be that in dollar sign cash up
Psyche awakens and you can do it for the bit here. I'll put the being the gong banners on the chat
The chat say it's not working
Okay
Everybody donated five dollars. So I don't see that. Oh arbiter. Thank you. You're yeah, thank you arbiter
Yeah, I think Paulus dude is trolling because the super old super chats fine, too
Thank you guys for the super chat. I think he goes for the super chat. You're awesome
Yeah, come back up bro. Go come back up, man
While you left me
You my yeah, I'm like up here. Well, if you're alone, what if I hit on the LES and it makes him uncomfortable
No, no, no, no, no, no, I think we're alone now. It doesn't seem to be anyone around
I think we're alone now your goals. You didn't have a heart. It's the only sound
I didn't kick you bro. Come on. Oh
Here is his back home
Yeah, what's up, Brody?
You know I was messing with
you, right?
Listen, what I've done tonight
is destroyed random guy.
He's called my boy,
this is the reason why I was
here tonight, which I've done
my, I've done my,
Yeah, yeah, you pretty much did yep. Yeah, he was done
But he was just a dick, you know random guy well anybody else wants to be a dick. I'm here
Shit hey
Last one last one on final Ninja Turtles sucks suck psyches fucking 50 year old wrinkled fucking cock
I'm not 50 years old. No, not me. No, you're sucking on my cock. You heard. Okay. Well, yeah
It's gonna crash the fuck out you're
No problem, I've seen
Yeah, he said
Everybody's on the panel suck cock. Yo, that's fucking crazy
Your ghost that means suck cock you on the panel you suck up
Well, that's something I guess as long as I'm here. I guess I suck psyche Scott at this point
No, but ain't nobody
Listen
Yeah, but listen up. I like you. Yeah, you call me. You're gonna call a side. Yeah, bitch. You know, call me a bitch
Chop psyche
And potatoes
or pride to see what is it
Can you please being random guy? I burnt his ass up. It was he's right. He was up here. He's like he was up here
Yeah, yeah, he said he said yeah, oh my he's like you bitch again
Yo, go thank you. I said you suck cop. That's it. Okay guys. Can we like be like let's let's like weird
Let's just like talk normally
Arguing to be friendly me and random guy. Yeah, he called you a bitch. I'm gonna handle it
But me and you are here. Yeah, we can argue. It's friendly. It's friendly
There I put all four in them. You're
I can how you represent other panels awesome. I'm gonna keep it 10 toes and I'm finna
Talking bro. Yeah goes down goes represent represent represent all the other pandas dumb dumb
Well, you should probably tell Psyche how I defend them on all their other panels. You dumb fuck.
So you saw how you go on people's panel and then you...
So name one time that I talk shit about Psyche on any other panel. Go ahead.
I didn't say you was talking shit about Psyche.
Play the clip. Play the clip.
You said it.
Play the clip.
I never said you was talking shit about Psyche.
I never say yeah, I always
I went again. You go to
you act the same way on this
I do act the same way but I also
I'm not saying why you act the same. I say why you act the same way.
Oh god, it feels good to be fucking
let's go argue. Are you dumb?
Why are you always? No, I thought I was dumb. I thought I was dumb
I wouldn't want to argue but when you get drunk when you drunk why you always want to argue with somebody
Why you can't have a normal conversation without you want to fucking be a dumb dumb
If you get drunk, why do you want to shake somebody's hand? I don't shake nobody's hand when I'm drunk
Okay, if you get drunk, why do you want to clap people?
When I get drunk, why do you want to love your momma?
You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You're listening to me. You
You dumb dumb dumb and stupid. Yo, I ain't gonna cover you cuz you fucking your target. It's okay
You don't know how to make
I'm quiet I'm quiet
Yeah, it's not the fuck I'm gonna stay like that. Okay. Make your argument. I'm quiet. Go ahead. I'm not argue with you, bro
Why I'm gonna argue with you and you act like a retard
It makes sense. I mean argue. Well, you could have been respectful. You could have been respectful
All right, well you act well listen dumb dumb now
Okay, what do you want to talk about sir
Let's have a normal conversation
No, I mean like what we always do
Well, okay argue back and forth. You know what for the first time in my life. I like I like I'll you all accept it
We can have a no more conversation with you. I agree with you, bro. I like don't don't take advantage brother
I'm telling you
Listen, I like how you set that to the
About when he sets a cycle and you want anyone like that. I mean, are you gonna be nice or not?
I'm having a normal come here. Are you gonna be my mother fucker? You're gonna be nice or not
I ain't gonna fucking beg you. You're gonna be nice or not. I really told you I am being nice
Well, more nicely you want one to buy that fuck if you I'm now I get I didn't ask you to bow down
Not every once way fucking nobody you're not fucking nobody apartment for me to bad down to you
Yeah
I didn't hear that one. You're gonna be nice or not. I'm not y'all say I'm not going to fucking that down. I already won
It's fine. It's fine. I won big deal
Are you gonna talk to me nicely?
How do you feel about the new matrix movie how do you feel about that?
Well, but no one this this one although you told my two thousand twenty four one
Yeah, the two thousand twenty four one. Yeah, that's his garbage
Garbage
Yeah, I agree
How the original ones the vision won't wait that it and the new original ones were a peak
Clat, I mean great fucking movies. Yeah
Yeah
Especially the first one the first the first
Hey, New York the first matrix
Yeah, what'd you say?
You saw you know, you saw the movie. I know when you did last summer the new one
Nah, not a new one. I
Sheen the actors in it. So I know they're gonna read
You know what's crazy? It was this guy who just like the guy who did what you did last summer in New York City
He went to everywhere so calling y'all and ball walking chasing the people
Did he hook him? Did he hook him? Nah, he was chasing everybody screaming and running
Yeah, but he uses a hook. He didn't hook him
No, bro, he was chasing them like
He did it everywhere and everybody was scared. They said oh shit the movies come in real life
Oh, they're gonna kill us. I like y'all have done
How a person will help you and kill you dumb dumb
And it's a dumb no niggas is scaring people just scaring you. I mean they just give me a scared
There's a music our man will do with a big-ass sword and
And chase you with a mask. Well, you will you will you run or you just try to stay there and kill you? I
Mean listen if you want to survive I would run
Now I wouldn't run outside fighting and take the night paint or the sword stab them up
You know, I would do let's be honest, you know, I do I bought that nine
Ain't nobody coming at me no fucking hook or none of that shit. I'll burn his ass up
Everybody was talking about that shit. That's it was on yeah burn his ass up
He got he get night in his chest
Shake a man with some shit they were saying red a man or shaking man or something like that
Well, listen, you're gonna come at me all funky as soon as you take that step soon as you take a step too far
I'm gonna fucking burn you up. I'm I'm at least you'd be nine
Nerd
The psyche just left us
Look what you did
Smoking that go you were talking some sense though because I do I do appreciate what you said like yes
You fucking like somebody's coming. He's like a fucking like acts anything like what are you gonna do?
Well, I'm gonna pull my gun out. I'm like cock that bitch
Not gonna keep coming at me. I'm I'm putting on you just if you were in New York City, right?
You know, you can't carry. Yeah, right and a guy with a hug comes
I don't live in New York, but yeah, I do. I do. I do.
Casey, will you run or you will you will stay there and fight for the first time?
Why the fuck are you in this for?
What?
What's he in it?
What are you talking about? Somebody porn bomb?
No, nobody in porn bomb. He's just laying back. No, they're still live. I see people typing. Oh shit. All right. All right.
Okay, we're not backstage. We're not backstage. You're good
Well listen sir, I
Don't care where you live at. Well listen, sir
I live in not like like what's near or something like let's just say that
You're gonna come at me with a knife even if you don't hold it up, but you're gonna fucking advance towards me
I'm gonna burn you. I'm gonna shoot you
Yeah
Yeah, I know you agree with me by the way
Nah, bro, it's crazy. Yo, let's go to Camp Kempstool Lake, yo
You from our state New York goes
Now I'm from Indiana brother
Well, I'm coming in and coming to you
Well, I'm from West Virginia, but I live in Indiana
I was. I was. I was.
That's nothing with you
You know what the fuck that thing is like random guy, I we'd probably drink together to random guy
He's just retarded on landmine. I
Think everybody on YouTube be honest everybody on YouTube. I think they all cool people
How to sit down have a drink or whatever drink or have sit down in the rest of our whatever
We don't have a good conversation
Well, you jumped on psyche like there's a primal fucking. Let's run it
You know
Yeah
Yeah, I don't believe it is this only us soon and there's nobody else coming on
Yesterday they would pop and I see a lot of people on the panel yesterday I
Had to pay some money to open it up, I guess
I think is the panel is open.
What are you joining?
I don't know if they'll join, but hopefully someone will join.
I'll drop the link.
Oh, you scared the shit out of me, Psych.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Yeah, where?
Yeah, fuck it.
Let's run it.
Yeah, open it.
Okay, I'll open it up. Yeah, the person's coming up
But yeah, if you want if anyone wants to open the panel, it's it is like, you know
You can send $10 to the cash app and then I'll it'll be a sponsored. I appreciate that if anyone can
But I'll bring up the person right now. Hold on one second
Ten bucks to sponsor it
Yeah, you're a bit you're my bitch you're asking for you're my bitch. You're asking for money, sir
From anybody that wants to sponsor the panel you're asking for money
Right. Well, I'm like letting them know about the service. I have
Bye
He's just a jerk, I think you know, I think he's gonna actually gonna like
He's fine
But on ghost is cool people know for a little hot minute. I mean he just said oh look maybe I said if anyone wants to sponsor the panel
They can't but it's like you don't have to it's first. You know, it's like you pay to clap ghosts
Okay, no, you don't have to pay yet next okay
I think it's a lot that's why it goes left because he thinks like he thinks someone's gonna clap him
You still can't my ghost you didn't protect yourself too. Hey. Hey look it
Watch this
Hold on
Okay, well, hopefully everyone's good. Oh, yeah, this the link is pinned. I don't know who's asking for the pin again
Yeah, it's pinned it is you don't see it. It was not pinned on stream yard. It's only pinned on the live chat
Oh, so there you go. Oh
Well, but yeah, personal ghost you're welcome Becca. Oh, oh, oh, there you go. He sponsored it. Thank you ghosts there
I go sponsored it. Thank you so much
Thank you go. Thank you ghost
Your goals you being a bootlicker come up. He's he's sponsored. He's sponsored. Yeah. Thank you goes
Appreciate you. Oh, I got some nice tinnage. Thank you so much. Appreciate that
Let me see you just fix this ghost. Are you coming back up? Come on up. I'm go see
Okay
So anyone have enough but well it's his panel now on eggs and so yeah
The next three hours, okay, ghost is ghost is good for the next few hours
My shit up and then how it goes donate donate to me to motherfuckers
Right ghost
Well, it's you know, it's you know, it's sort of panel sort of panel and then
Goes I'm gonna start my pain when you donate to me to motherfucking
How did I just take this time to donate to you?
Absolutely nothing. I'll let you I'll let you run my pen on the whole day
Everybody off. Do you think I run it's like he's put your argument. Do you think I run it's like
Yeah, he beat me up for this money
Beat me up. No, he's there and don't lie. No, you just want to be exactly. So what's your argument you dumb fuck?
Can I built you up? Can I put new parts in you and New York? You're never gonna be I'm like you're
So like if you talk nice to me, I actually will give you a show. I'll actually join you're gonna be nice
No, I'm not being nice. I don't got a panel. No, that's boy
You're her you pussy boy
Fuck boy. I
Kind of like when Elias talks to me like that though
What what the fuck? Oh, you're talking to go so shit. Sorry. Yeah
Yeah, talk to me real dirty like that you're
Showing your mouth
Jack Jack please
Please give me the
Give me the door jack, please
Just like I did with the random guy I'll do it to you. I'll fucking
That was rude that's me. Oh my god, that's my thing. It's actually
I got a bottle of liquor for you. You want it? Yeah, let's drink it
drink it and get drunk, right?
and party like a rock star,
right? Well, maybe you should
not drink it. Maybe you should
to shut the fuck up. No, I
just took the shit out of you,
bro. You're drunk. I just,
yo, when I'm drunk, I just
put it on. I'll put it on.
So on them, you're I took the
show and I'm here. I'm here.
Listen up. I'll put you on a
t-shirt. You keep talking here.
Bro, I'll take the I'll take
the belt and spank you.
**** you mean **** you mean
**** you mean I just **** you.
I'll put your shirt, sir. I'll
I'll smoke. I'll this one sir.
I'll smoke on your pack. Oh, I
will smoke on your pack.
Yeah, I'll smoke it.
Oh my gosh. Yeah, you're I smoke on the LSD, you know, let's not even know. Oh, yes, imagine that I'll smoke on a pack
Bro, bro. I'll just burn you up. Yeah, you want me to like fuck it. I'll send a smoke. I'm send a smoke on your
Yeah, you try
I'm talking right now. Listen, you're a smoke. Yo, you're a smoke on my these nuts. Oh my gosh
I'm not. I'm not. I'm not.
You sound like you're gobbling. No, go, go, go, go, go. That's what you sound like. That's the idea
What I was supposed to do I came here to descend. It's like what you did you came you came up here
You're gobbling it on the
The nuts is all in your mouth my dude I
Don't know what you mean
You don't know what you mean
No
No, I'm not talking about you. So, I'm talking about the guy the guy the guy who was arguing with. He left. Yeah
You got getting his nuts right now
Can't we all just get along?
No, why you can't get along
Well, cuz he called psyche a bitch and I whooped his ass, but keep me get along now. All right, buddy
But now you're repeating yourself. Oh, all right. All right. What a broken record. All right, what?
You want you want you want to you want to be his cheeks or something?
Yeah, you just saw you just you just want to stick it raw in his butthole and
What you want to say?
I would like to defend my friend and none of you
Matter of fact, I'll make the argument you Lisa's butthole. I have it so make the argument. Yo
The flow. Yo, yo, he's back. He's back. He's at my boy
And back chat my boy
Yo, that's that was a dick. I thought that was a dick. That was his fucking wrinkly hand. Did you guys see that?
I thought that was a dick for I swear of my life. No
That's hands holy shit psyche any who hey, um, who's that guy talking about black guy? Who's that black guy?
He's not black. He's Puerto Rican. His name is the Puerto Rican guy. What's up, dude?
I don't know what I don't know nonions. Any who welcome welcome back. No
No, when you were doing that shit that go go go go go ghost got so quiet because he was like literally thinking about sucking a dick
He didn't know what to say. Yeah, like there was like a there's like a whole dick in his brain when you did that
I was watching I was listening. I was working right now. He didn't know what to say, dude
He was fucking struck with data
Do you paralyze him with
I'm out of here. I just got I that was funny dude. Keep keep it up. I'm listening. Why are you here? Why are you here?
Alright see you said
Fucking faggot let him back up. Hey, don't say that word goes come on
Fucking dumb dumb. Yo, put the cock in your mouth and gog away
I already fuck it. It's like he already destroyed that guy. Yeah. No, you didn't. No, you didn't
You just destroyed how did I how did I not how did I not you got the you got the cargo nuts in your mouth?
Did I destroy him yes or no, no, you had enough in your mouth
So I did I well, let me ask you
Get no psych psych. Don't get involved. Okay, sir. Let me I'm asking you
Destroy him yes or no
Okay, I didn't you saw him
Who wants to debate? Let's do it
You want to be the one dear do you? Oh you?
You don't go good nuts. No, I already won
No, you didn't. You gogled a
bitch. You can't. You ain't
You're my bitch. No, you're my
You're too stupid to have to
Goggled a nuts. Goggled a nuts.
I am going to have to go to
I am glad I came here. I am glad I came here.
Love you go
Yo, go remember have a dream about King Kong cookies. Yeah, I'll be in your mouth
Debate brother
Okay, what do you want and think about the King Kong? No, no, no fuck it. Let's run it
Do you want to run it sir?
Do you want to run it think about the King Kong cookies? Yeah, do you want to run it sir?
You want to run the King Kong cookie in your mouth sir?
All right, so I guess by the way that dude's never gonna call you a bitch again
You want and also that dude's stuck in your car. It's like yeah, appreciate you for having me up. Thank you
Ghosts love you. Have a good night
Well, if they're talking shit this uh, I'll join it goes your bitch go to sleep go night night
He's nice man. He's a nice guy.
He's nice.
We're crushing each other like, like we buddies, you heard?
Yep.
Yep, it's fun.
Well, I guess like that, uh...
Why is it guy with the fake New York accent is Hispanic? I don't know. He's just a Puerto Rican
I don't know. I don't think it's actually a snake. Oh my me. Yeah
Say no, no, I'm not Puerto Rican. I'm black
He's black
Okay, whatever whatever
Thank you so really saw my face. I saw you. Yeah, you came out you came up on like betas
We sure
Yeah
You never came up over here and I was like you were on beat us or think beat us or like some other channel
And I was like, oh, there he is like
You anyway, you went there right after mine. You went there after my show
I want I want I want the Jeff. I want the Jeff arm and
Jeff, okay
And then I want to Dave Dave pen
the arm
Dave, I don't know. No, it was like I don't I want to know a jeff or Dave
I don't go to like many shows like I go like just to go to a few as well
They don't come on. They don't do arm. They don't do panels like they don't do like like the way you do it
They don't do it all friends. You know, I mean they come once in a while
They go and do the panel and then yeah, you know, they get born palm and then they they shut their thing down
They they come back up and then you know, there's a lot of dumb stuff
Yeah, I just come on the planet that have conversation or sometimes the bugger
And so I want to curse with this curse, you know after conversation, whatever
Yep
I'm happy to chat. I'm happy to come up and chat. Let's let me see
Yesterday I was on a different panel
For a little bit and then when I went to your panel you ended so my poem on you. I think you ended. Yeah
I get tired of like getting form bomb. It's it's stressful because it's like
Realize when they palm bomb you that's messing up your YouTube panel. Thank you for the donation arbiter. Thank you so much
You're so sweet. I love you
Well, I'd say for for oh for yeah. Oh, thank you
Yeah, like the LES is a good guy and
Thank you LES too. I appreciate that for
You know inspiring ghosts. Thank you so much guys, and if you
You know how I met ghost be honest with you on the arm on the podcast I go to
Mm-hmm, that's what people's podcast. Yeah, I'm not I'm there and he is this a trick
Yeah, he's a trip and he's a good guy though, and it's like you know
he's been very supportive of the show and
I've always appreciate ghosts and what a great great soul. Thank you ghosts. You're very sweet. Oh stay on bro
Here he comes. He's coming back here
I'm here now
He was saying nice things about you. He's saying he met you on the people's podcast or something like that and you're a cool guy
He thought you were fuck the people's podcast
No, fuck you asshole
Your her ghost put my big cock in your mouth I heard it pretty clear fuck the people's podcast
Yo, and then fuck you too suck my big cock motherfucker
You're her go go that shit too guys are just getting along so well
Nah, he want to be a dickhead and you know, I will never say that to nobody's panel about nobody's panel
But he's a fucking asshole
Ghost why'd you say something about the people that's that's kind of rude. Yeah, but I'm gonna tell you like this goes
But yeah, you're talking about dumb, but lucky. Yeah, I don't care
We get the same you was on that panel. You was on that panel sucking my dick nigga. I was on that
You was
Yo, I wasn't talking about him. I never knew about
Don't ask motherfucker. I don't know about sake. Oh, yeah, I don't care. I don't care. Don't ask motherfucker. Yeah
I don't care. I don't my dick. Okay. I don't get
Very good. I don't care. Go suck a dick. That's right. That was real
Fuck you rich
Fuck you. Oh god
dick bitch
Why did you turn on ghosts now you turn on just you turn on ghosts now
You're just saying I say nice. Oh, I'll be I'm being just like go damn. He's crashing out
Is this a guy from the people's podcast? Are you like the owner? Who's that guy the owner of people?
I'm not your bro. I'm not the owner, but
If I'm on your panel and your name was
Yo, shut the fuck up check his name
Yo, I see it
When I go to your panel and stop crashing out when I go to a different panel and someone's talking about your panel
You're literally like you will let you be up here. Let's be cool
Let him
It's like he's being on that mine. Go suck up. You can be up here stop crashing the fuck out
Go suck a dick, bro. Go suck a dick suck your dry dogs
Yeah
You just drunk running you running your mouth crashing the fuck
Yo, shut up, bro
All right, no don't think you don't think you big Willie does you give me money out bro?
You're not big Willie. You just human just like everybody else
Would you like some money man? You're mad you man? You don't got a panel and you can't do
The fuck out of it, bro, that's you know
That's why you don't okay in your mouth
I saw you got my dick in your mouth. Go put my dick back in your mouth.
All right, all right.
You little, you little fucking sweet cheeks. You sweet cheeks.
All right.
And you was in jail with me, I'll make you be my bitch. Shade up like that, bro.
How you like that, bro?
You heard?
You wouldn't be talking to people like this on the podcast and you was in jail, bro.
Now you got me started, bro, but no fucking reason you want to run your mouth now. You're
My little girlfriend super fuck up put my dick back in your mouth. Yeah
Put my dick in your mouth man psyche drive for mission
Yeah, well, you want so psyche to kick me? Oh, that's him. What the fuck are you talking to you like that here?
straight up
Fucking bitch nobody trying to kick you off. You don't fuck go nobody try to kick you off
Suck a dick bitch. Nobody's trying to kick you off. Yo, I try to kick you off
Fuck up my bitch. I tried my bitch. Yeah, I ain't suck at nothing here
So my dick back your little sister sucked on mine, but maybe next time maybe she's stuck on yours. Here
You don't like what the fuck try to kick you. I'll take your little ass. I'll fuck you in your little ass
Please explain what you're saying. No, you might
Bend over and you bend over and spit your teeth. Oh my god
It's like random guy. They like to say that like you're my bitch. Please explain. You are my bitch
You are my bitch, ghost. Please explain. You are my bitch. You remember that you might be explain
You my bitch for tonight. You heard
Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god
You're you're you're you're my pet. You're my pet dog. A hundred eighty-five. That's your master, bitch
Listen to your master. Who's Nova?
dumb bitch
Now who bitch you is monst like you're gonna have to take that. That's your argument. You're
Yes, you're right
No, if you're asking my I wouldn't have them up here, okay
Well, never mind
God damn, dude, I
Mean you're just arguing to argue. You're not even making any sense, dude
I mean, he was saying like the he was just saying threats. Oh, yeah, it's not making any sense at all
Making threats like it's offensive to gay people. It's offensive to straight. I'm sorry psyche
I gave you a couple dollars. Do you feel do you feel offended by me giving you a couple dollars?
Do you feel it's a no?
No, it's helping me. It's helping the show. I take it and you're not like holding it like saying, oh, you're my bitch now and stuff
What the fuck is the argument then? I don't understand. There's no argument. They don't have an argument
Do I run your panel? Do I run your panel? No, not at all. Not at all. Not at all.
Whatever it is, I like I fuck is the problem then. There's no problem
It's just people like to say like to talk shit, you know
God damn signals. He's retarded, but at least he's so I could misretard it
We got to talk about these retarded people and I think they're okay
Yeah
Yeah, but we love I love ghosts and thank you for
Thank you for that. Yeah, there was a there was a fake siffa in the chat. That was a fake siffa there
Getting also some interesting messages. Let me just go through the messages real quick. Oh
Put it on me
I'll put on you. No, no, I was just looking at my I'm sorry
Yeah
Why guys you can hang out with ghosts. He's right here. Let's see. Oh, I'm not
Yeah, LES, I mean, it's like, you know, we're cool still but it's just like you know, yes, you can join again
Just stop with that bullshit, dude
No, he's gonna keep doing it, but you know go ahead
With them fucking I'm not paying for nobody to come up here, then okay?
Oh, you guys you say bullshit every fucking time
I'm sorry to crash I was like you but every fucking time
Yeah
Okay, yeah, but I love your ghost. Thank you like for everything, you know, you're
There you want to call him a bitch? Well, let's run it
And thank you Vicky that I think he's putting my tick tock
I do have a cool tick tock on page now. I was already on today
You know, I did a little bit of our show Michael on again tonight
Like it's fun because I just like to do readings and stuff like that and it's like and you know
And promote that side of my personality and stuff. I know not everyone's into carbs here, but
You know, I am really like a believer in tarot and I'm, I'm, I'm actually, I'm sitting here
descending everyone.
You want, you want some cards?
You want some cards?
Ghost, I got you some cards.
Okay.
So this is one.
One.
Okay.
For haters exposed deck, your card is.
Animal.
Animal card.
It says, oh, animal card.
Well, this already says envious of your career and the money you make.
Okay.
Hmm.
So they're envious of you.
You know, you want an animal card?
Oh, I have to grab it.
Okay, let me see
Mmm animal car oh your animal spirits, okay
Your animal card is a
Who you got a bear or be a bear the bear yeah, let's go
It's a symbolism healing divinity. Oh
vulnerability
The bear has symbolized divinity and healing in many cultures.
I'm a people of northern islands of Japan, believe the bear was a mountain god.
India bears are believed to prevent disease. Children may ride on a bear's back to prevent sickness.
Among the Fina, Ugric's people, he's the god of heaven.
The bear has figured prominently in Native American peoples who regarded as a spirit being.
and the hunting of the bear woman dancing with the tatt the rattle recalls a
Pauly Indian story of bear medicine woman in which a girl
Born with the bear spirit has a power to heal. So there's a bear right there. Oh
That was her cubs
Yeah, well, yeah, she's a power to heal and yeah, the bear mother is like your mama bear, right?
It protects the cubs. I am the bear. It's like I fucking child. So I do the code you bitch. That's what I want
Yeah, well here's here. He's back. Do you want to talk to him? Yeah? Yeah, I'll fucking run it with him. Let's run
Let's make some money right here. Hey, uh, so ghost let's do it. I have an argument. Yeah
It's made benefit. How long well one question. I'll let you I'll let you answer it one question, though
How long did you think about the argument?
I'm working right now
You don't have
So here's the thing goes ask it. Yeah, go ahead check this out
Okay, so baby
psyche
Like you listen to me boy listen to me boy
Me we're gonna do a cash up off like you don't let her up here. She talked all that shit
You're gonna let both of them up there. I love them
Money right now in cash shop
You want to challenge me there's two people
I like this game already. I like this game. Okay. Let's hear one shot. You get one shot
one blind
And the loser
You're not
On your panel again. Oh, come on. Okay. That's a good deal. I like that. I don't know. I didn't have it here
What was the I don't know? I sounded like a challenge and I was like let's just agree to it challenge data. Shut the fuck up
Jesus Christ you always should
No, he's not no he's not
You can do where the fuck he wants with it. You're lucky. You know, I know I'm asking you. Do you guys want to leave?
Are you up for a ghost?
In the next five minutes
I agree win and the loser is banned indefinitely
Let's that's all quit whoever sends the most money in the next five minutes
Then what?
We win though you never coming back beta still gonna be a dumb fucking bitch. She's still got nothing
She's still not a haul dumb
Oh, I'm warning you ghosts you better come high. We're not talking about hundreds
Came high
Or we can have a conversation what would you like to talk about? No
There is no conversation. This is going nowhere.
Sike, you're a bitch. You run the fucking panel.
I'm about to dethrone you.
Sike, he just...
You're about to be dethroned.
Sike, you just got caught up.
Sike, are you okay with this?
Let's play the game
Six and stones, I'm not I'm gonna fit the bad guys good games. I'm all playing around you ain't gonna call psyche a bitch no more
Way more than you do right now
I heard you
So I come up like you bitch. Go ahead. How is it? Let's go. Let's go. Let's fucking go. You're gonna call my boy a bitch
How is he a bitch?
And therefore I don't understand what's about to happen ghost
How was I think you understand what is about to happen right now ghost you're about to never
I don't think you understand what the fuck is going on the house like okay?
You've got five minutes
How was like well fuck you I want fucking 10 seconds fuck you I don't want you're gonna fucking put that on me house like you bitch
You were calling him earlier you were calling him
I was like, oh
Psyche baiters. Oh fuck. What's wrong? You weren't in the chat. I was in the side. You're like, you're my best
No, he's no one's beta. By the way, you do talk about beta is beta
I'll beat, uh, one bucket of beer, but, uh, you talk a lot of shit, too.
And you come over there and you just sit there and you talk a lot of stuff.
I'll beat, uh, beta.
I already whooped some ass early.
You're out of the worst of beta.
Yeah
What do you mean psyche don't talk to him I'm the one that has no way oh now we can't talk to psyche now you're just gonna
Well you have as far as I know yeah, I never heard you say anything negative about me, but is it true you said I was money
And also I just finished Mike correct
Okay, well, thank you. I appreciate it. And now you're gonna fall because the data is here
beta
I don't you're a fucking fool. I don't give a fuck what your name is. You're disgusting. Don't don't
You're just please don't please don't call her name. Yeah. Is that why you joined my panel in psyche?
Is that why you why you joined when psyche's not live?
Psyche is live you don't have nowhere else to go
What do you mean by that? Go ahead and explain. You have what you have selective memory. Okay. Let's talk about selective memory
Listen
Yeah, because I'm not trying to get you to control my ass.
Nobody wants to control you.
I just want an argument.
Can you argue or not dumb dumb?
Well, let's run it.
All right, let's run it.
Okay, what's your argument?
That you're a dumb dumb.
So you won argument because thank you. Thank you very much. Yay. I got one point
How did you win how did you win please explain because I shut you up for two seconds and that was pretty
How did you win you dumb fucking?
Don't mess. How do you win careful? I you're dumb dumb. No, that's not careful. How do you win?
I just called you a dum-dum.
Same people that call psyche a bitch and sister for no, how did you win?
Psyche a bitch earlier, and I can prove it because I was
You were arguing with random guy, and you're like, no
He's been only in the back. Yeah, I heard it. Okay, you're claiming it. I never once got psyche a bitch
You're a liar now, too. I
Actually join goes actually join and defend him. I never want some of it. Don't cry. Don't cry. You'll be okay close
Don't be okay. Thank you. It's like did I ever once got you a bitch?
Not that I heard
psyche remember
You go maybe you'll be like I'll be just in bed. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, he did
I got your back on that. I got you. I know what's your argument though. Yeah, you got proven wrong. So uh second of all
What's your argument? I can't move it, right?
Yeah, you're not gonna prove it right. All right, go ahead. It's the same stream. Thank God
He hasn't been porn bomb so you can rewind back
So what's your argument that I want another never cuts like
Shut up. I've never once got him. Okay. Okay. Okay. I
You got you bored me already. I'm bored. I'm bored. I'm bored. You're fucking an aqua holocaust. Yeah
I like um, I never want to add them
Huh, you're too stupid to have the conversation. What do you want to talk about idiot? What a psyche you want to talk about?
There's hold on I can't put anybody. I don't know on I'm gonna
Cuz I just want to save my
So be careful right now
But yeah, but I love you guys, you know, I don't think it bends vibe. It's like there's people that
Yeah, the people that don't fuck with me, there's people that do fuck with me and it's like it's like so I've been here
No, I mean fuck with me in a good way, you know where it's like, you know
Thank you. Did I not defend you?
Yeah, you did. I mean, I appreciate it.
Are you gonna ask the same question like 10,000 times before you annoy the fuck out of him?
As soon as you leave.
So oh, I think that's okay. I'll leave I'll leave I'll leave soon as you believe you can ask like you all to yourself
No, no, no, he's calling me a lesbian retarded. What's it? No, no, no
Does that way to make fun of somebody
You don't know how to be friends with somebody what if I called you
Ma'am I have clips of you talking shit about
Really? I'm here. I'll clip from you on my channel trying to buy friendships from me
It has nothing to do with psyche though. Meow and then earlier
No, I don't I always see she really talked shit about you know psyche knows everything he watches anyways
Alright guys, we're gonna remember that next time we will you lost another
Okay, how about this? You can win this argument if you tell me to leave. They go, go leave,
Vita. You'll win the argument. It's psychies. You want me to tell you? Exactly. So meow, stop it.
No, listen, bitch. Let's have a conversation. No, you're the bitch, bitch. See, this is how I
know you call somebody a bitch because you've been calling people bitches all night, bitch.
Well, you are retarded, ma'am.
I have a higher IQ than you
so
Okay, go ahead and prove it
Okay
What's your I2? Okay, I'll go ahead
So prove it
What is your IQ?
Perv it
Okay, what does IQ stand for you're not good. Are you gonna prove it or not?
Well, you don't even know what it is. So how are you going to prove it prove it prove it?
I am trying to prove it. I'm asking you some questions right now
Try to do it in the don't try to do it and just fucking do it. What does IQ stand for?
You're not gonna do you fucking make that
If you don't even know what IQ stand for then how the fuck you know that you'll have a higher
Pervit go ahead. Go ahead. I just did
Dum-dum, you're not gonna do nothing. You said nothing here. Oh my god poor psyche has to deal with this
Oh my well. Yeah poor psyche. I'm okay. There's somebody back stage. I want to talk to you less running New York
Is that easy? No, I want to tell you
No, you lost an argument your argument is done
Name one. All right. What what argument?
I can play any trivia with you and you'll lose all the
because I already played all the trivia.
Well, I'm gonna fuck that.
What argument did I lose?
All of them.
Yeah, name one, dumb fuck.
What's your argument that I lose?
Well, I'm trying to leave right now and you're trying to keep me to stay because you-
They won't leave. Why are you talking shit?
No, I won that. I won the debate.
I won the debate. Yeah.
What argument did I leave? You don't know what the fuck you're talking about.
I'm talking to you. Thank you, there.
Yep, I'm here. Okay. Okay. I'll let you go. So you're talking about yours. Yeah
You know what it's time write down on a piece of paper five
I lose go ahead. I think you definitely lose what?
argument
Every single argument dumb dumb
So I keep what argument did I lose I don't know what's going on
Because you make no, yeah, fuck she's talking about
Did I lose what are you please explain it?
You don't the fuck you're talking about you. Yeah, you kind of stupid
Shit is easy. Hold on. Hold on. We have one second. We have random guy back. What up, dude?
So did you get the cash up or no? Hold on one second. Let me check. I didn't see you. What is that random guy?
Yeah, I got the tech I got the tech around noise. Don't worry about it. Get the test
Okay, so did I win I mean I always
What did he send?
Okay, well, you know nothing so okay, so
He said he said he said 20 today though. He said 20 22 actually
So that I said in the next five minutes, so he lost technically, you know, did you send more than 20 random guy?
I didn't know about that 20. He didn't bring that up
That wasn't part of the fucking argument
Ghost you lose once again
Straight to the point beat. I like that about you. That was funny
The argument is that you lose
Yeah
Yeah, I'm back on the panel when you were close to your out. You're done. So
On the panel. I'm not going nowhere
What do you like to prove me wrong indefinitely, dude
He's back on he's back on he's all about money good and prove me wrong. I'm leaving where
They're going anywhere
Nowhere
Anyway, thank you for losing the argument once again
I'll talk to you random guy by psyche
You can't debate
Her how about that just because you said we don't want to fuck you thank you very much
Okay, maybe
You don't yeah, but a matter of fact you talked about it shit about psyche. Honestly, I've joined your panel a couple times
And you keep repeating the same thing
No, it's not that it's not a lot of shit about like played out. That's what it really is a lot of shit about
Like yeah, huh?
I need to lose another argument dum-dum it is my business
If I talked a lot of shit about psyche, why are you my panel my last life and you're up there the whole time?
I'm trying to control it and you
I don't know. I don't know.
don't know. I don't know. I
Because she said so that's how she only that's that's what she said
All right, what's your argument?
Is that a sim you're ever here saying I'm protecting so you were literally saying
Go ahead. What's your argument? That is the argument
Because she said so and I think everyone everyone's embarrassed
And that's psyche is letting you own him for that almighty dollar you are too stupid to sell out
You're too stupid. He is definitely your bitch. I'll give you that. I will give you that
Psychic you're my bitch. How do you feel about that? It's my bitch, too
I'll be everybody's bitch for a dollar
Nope, I'm not
Your dick and porn bomb as long as you send enough money to psyche
It's open panel correct
If you want to
It's okay. No, you're fine. You're fine.
No, I'm just saying. Can I, can I do it? Yes or no? Yes, you can. Yes, you can.
Listen, who the fuck are you talking to? You don't know what the fuck is happening.
You don't even know what cash up is happening. Let's run that bitch, Doug.
Go sit the cash up. Two fucks is stupid to do it.
Two fucks is stupid to do it.
Ghost.
What is he gonna buy a 20 20 20 bucks? Okay? Yeah, 20 bucks. Nobody's gonna buy a fucking sweetest fish
Nobody gave $20 you dumb fuck the burden of first would be on you. I was told you made the claim
The guy running the stream said you gave him $20. Is that true psyche?
Yes, not tonight. Okay, then that's not the argument that I win. I don't know what this guy
I'm not cash up. I can't have anything. I can't have a conversation with him. Okay. Well, he's saying I didn't give him $20
Now you really have fucking regarded. You don't understand what it means
What I
Like this song read you want me to repeat myself
You sound drunk. No, actually. I mean, that's what drunk people do. Go ahead. Repeat yourself. That's what drunk people do.
Go ahead. Well, that's what he wins. And guess what? Guess what? I won that one.
Yard? By the way, psyche we always win. Yeah, psyche always, psyche and ghost always win. Yeah, we always win, brother.
Anybody else? Everyone good? Everyone good? Everyone?
So we're all having a good night. I don't I don't want to fight with anybody anymore
I like I love you guys. We can all get along, but you guys want some trouble. Let's run at me. It's like the oldest one
There anybody out there, I'm down to get along
Well, the music actually calms me down. I don't know about him
Yeah, play that music I'm playing this game. The game is like it's like it's like it's like a koi fish game
You're a koi fish like eating like little other fish and like just going on really slow
But you get faster when you get like level up. It's kind of fun game. Call my boy a bitch
They suck, you know what they're never gonna do never gonna call you a bitch again
Straight up. I'll fucking lick his ass. Just call them a bitch like four times on this
I've never once thought psyche a bitch first of all second of all nobody else is gonna call psyche a bitch
That's me. That's my brother. That's my friend and they got his back and they're never gonna call him a bitch. Oh
Shit psyche. Oh
Hey, oh my gosh, I wanted to say hi to you but my TV's on I don't know how to like
I have to like find the remote
I think I usually smoke cigarettes outside. Hold on. Let me find a light it
I'm acting manic
Exciting you have me on screen
There's a real teeth aren't they crystal the real teeth, huh? Yeah
Huh come on
What kind of teeth are there? All my real teeth. Oh, what kind of teeth are they your mommy ask it a hundred percent mine. Oh
Are they crowns you got some crowns or these
Okay, they are I
Got them from my dentist
Oh, yeah, that's really good. Okay. I did two years of doing
Do you know what direct or um, oh, yeah, I can't be your friend
Right, okay. What's that? And then they give you one final fucking thing, right?
Final fucking thing, right? Yes. Anyway. Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, and in small words this is the final thing
Well, yeah, yeah, listen listen listen, so so they do put the plastic in for like a couple months, right?
Yes, I know what that is
Okay, you don't have to you don't have to you got the real ones now, huh? No, I have a real teeth
100% all my real teeth
Yeah, they put the years it's like the nearest you have the nearest over your teeth, right?
Yeah, oh they're for near
It's like when you go to beauty school
Are they veneers or are they crowns or some more money?
It's like
The other because I can't I'm not do I can't afford that dude, which you know where
Hold on. Can you finish can answer the question?
Please
Sure, veneers or crowns or you know, okay dentures
Want to call them that one of them
No, no, no, no, no, please crystal learn better like crystals. I'm not even being fucking mean
I don't want the dental school
Fucking are a fucking smile or whatever it was called
Clips or flip right give you one final one they give you one final one and this is it can you take them out?
Yeah
Okay, so they're not like the four on four implants. Okay, but I have all my fucking
That doesn't make any sense if you said you have dentures, then now you're saying you have all your teeth
I'm highly confused right now. I
really am
They attach to your teeth, right? They attach to your teeth. They hook in, right?
Oh
They're called flippers. Are they called flippers or flips? That's what the sweepy said. Yeah, they're called flippers
That's what trash has to trash is missing her front two teeth
I don't know if you know that same with amber. Thank you girls. Thank you so much. Yes. We're talking about
Amber so thing your friend trash is missing her front two teeth. She's actually missing four teeth
Okay, actually treasure is four teeth missing. I have every one of my teeth. I didn't have to go that far
Did you get them shaved down like a little shark teeth for the flippers a
Little bit
But I had already been in a really bad accident where my
mouth was in a fun. I had perfect teeth by the way
That sucks
But you had an accident
Yeah, I was an accident. I lost
Like people died in it too as well when people like to troll me on this and people died
Yeah, not the best
Are we in trouble? Yeah, it's not the best rule. Oh, ho someone died and you got a car. Oh, that's kind of fucked up
You know I'm saying
And they use that and it hurts me so hard, you know what I mean
Oh, you probably shouldn't have told me you um
You're in a car with a bunch of debt. You probably shouldn't have said that, you know
It'll watch what you say. Well people know that you've already know that and I don't have
Nah, dude, I'm not gonna repeat. I'm not a repeat fucking repeat bitch
Okay, if you don't know then you don't know and I don't care I
Care about you right now like listen
my gosh clarity
With psyche psyche give me like he doesn't even know when he gave me clarity
And he gave you clarity
Psyche gave you clarity. Yeah, he did. That's
That's not good. Thank you so to page
I could see that one
Oh come on, friend, don't insult me, please
Don't insult me, I don't like being insulted about my real life
She's a little more normal than you are, I'm just saying
She's more sound-minded than you
I'm not crazy, sometimes it's like
When I go more connected to you, psyche
Oh thank you, thank you so much
Yeah, I just like you know people that could be criticized at me and it's like I think that it's like it doesn't like
What a psychic isn't necessarily a normal person sometimes
They're a little bit crazy because they are like getting messages from the spirit world and things like that
And so people will laugh at them and say they're oh, that's persons weird or whatever, but I'm an honest person
I'm not really charged on but I try to do most of my stuff for free without asking for anything
And so it's like I don't know why people like continually what I want to say
I'm like some kind of bad person for
and you're not at all like it makes me sad that people like you know like this is the way the
world works you know honestly because there's people that attack uh when it's not worth it you
know what i mean and you know why and guess what psyche this is why people get hurt
Like Christine is gonna get hurt bad. Well, don't know that's right. Who's what he's saying about Christine Christine's
Well, I'm Christine's a great wonderful lady
Well because she keeps fucking with me, dude
I don't know why she keeps fucking with my energy, but she doesn't know that I have a stronger energy than anybody
It's like you're you're catching some black backlash for not letting the people of color on it's okay
It's no, it's okay. I'm gonna I'm gonna and I won't say end the stream that I'll bring a problem
I'm probably let off the POC's because
I'm ending this all in the stream
You know I go on here with no makeup and these bitches like I want to talk about my face and make my face
They're fucking brutal file. We'll make it
Yeah
Guys don't talk to me and Chad. They're talking to me and Chad like very demanding about come on panel
I can have people on the panel who I want you right now, and so maybe you should tell crystal Marie
That's why you're catching all this backlash because you're letting this ghost guy own you with money
There we go, that's that's the
I can't I can't hear the person. Let's go. Let's go
Okay, let's go
Crystal you're gonna do whatever the fuck he wants to do crystal you get high
I get drunk. You know what? Honestly, I get I've been getting
I on gummies. I am like so fucking paranoid. That's fine.
I was talking like other stuff. Okay, cool. I never do drug.
I never done a drug except for them. Recently and then they
told me like paranoia like I can't smoke weed.
For better than I am
Because I was gaming people like smoke reading it or like what what do what is it?
What are they putting in the lead right now? It's like very strong isn't it like almost like heroin?
It's like so strong. It's like puts you right to sleep. I mean you might just sleep for sure like you know
It's like very strong. Oh
California super strong
I want to know what I'm smoking or I'm not going to smoke it or it's going to make me paranoid and I don't want to do fucking drugs to buy on the street like just don't smoke it.
That's what I'm saying I never I haven't smoked dude.
You just said you took on like 10 years or something wait.
So she's not smoking it, but she's taking gummies. So she's like separating the two like they're different, but they're really really nauseous
When I'm strode like I have an anxiety attack. I have a really high anxiety
Uh-huh. So
Alcohol is like really good a real accent
Like right now I'm fucking drinking alcohol in two weeks, dude. I'm super high off alcohol
You don't have a problem with drugs and alcohol. You just do it recreationally
That's what I'm here. Yeah, I just do it like too much
I mean, that's do that's fine
Well, you know what I mean though like when you like
I just like like the one time I do is like over
Now if you drink every day like ghosts, I think there might be a problem I might suggest, you know cutting back
I'm getting tired I woke up. It's
In the morning, dude
I kind of want to hear a crystal Marie talk instead of you
I'm gonna give a fuck what you want to hear you think you brought my name up so
Drinking on the weekdays is weird for me and I don't care
And I'm sorry guys. I'm sorry guys, but yeah, it's cool. I was psyche. I fucking love you, dude
Psyche, can I just bring it to psyche for one second? Yeah
Oh, my God, I'm out of psyche.
You look so handsome.
All of you are so handsome.
And I just, um...
Oh, you're so sweet.
You have a really great arms. Like you have really great arms like something to say
Crystal I literally thought when he like pulled his thumb up on stream. I thought it was a penis
Resembles maybe it resembles that but it's like, you know, it's like he was getting porn ball when I seen this
I was all old and wrinkly. I'd know if that's old and wrinkly. It's a normal
There was a little thumb. It's like, come on. Why are you being rude?
But I love you. I love you so much.
I'm getting so tired, dude.
OK, well, we're going to bed.
Get to just like pray and like you know meditate a little bit and they do some deep breathing
Maybe like a mantra a mantra on the phone
You know, I do like you know, I'll do like counseling sessions and stuff like that or no tarot and stuff like that over the phone
too privately if you'd like to so
Beautiful, oh, thank you. I love you. Thank you. Your sweetheart. Thank you so much
Crystal Marie. Have a good night. Have a good night you guys
Okay
She was a decent guess like she really that was a normal interaction, you know, I like crystal crystal is beautiful and very nice and
So we're here. Let me get some work done. Okay. I can't keep on out your stream and saving your fucking stream
So you need to let these up. Thank you for the
Thank you for the
Okay, I'll be locked up backstage. Love you. Love you guys